{
    "id": "9f8873b2b7b441bc97fd43e5513b532d",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The terrorists had planned to blow ……………………… the palace.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like it when she brought …………………….. the matter of divorce all over again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was brought ………………………. by his uncle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish they would call the meeting ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me to do the job ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We will have to find ……………………… who the real culprit is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The book store is giving …………………… used books.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "away",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When are you going to give me my money ……………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "again",
                "back",
                "back again"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The students have handed ……………………… their work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Armed men held ………………… the bank yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}